on January 25th I made
$96,000 in 4 hours with one single trade
I told everybody on my Instagram
telegram Discord everybody saw it and in
the following minutes I'm going to show
you exactly how I did it my thought
process behind the trade and the
strategy that I actually applied in
order to be able to make
$96,000 in Just 4 hours so to begin with
I want to explain to you a bit of my
thought process behind I take any trade
whether it's going to be a big one or
whether it's going to be a small one and
that's the first things first I treat
every single trade the same a lot of
people say oh I risk a lot of money for
a certain type of trade and then a
little B A money for a different type of
trade you shouldn't be doing that you
shouldn't be dividing risk for a good
trade or a bad trade you should never be
taking bad trades in the first place I
always take the same exact type of trade
that is my thought process behind
trading is I only take high probability
trade setups and that consists of very
simple steps one you have to follow the
trend the trend is your friend I know
you've heard it a million times and I
will repeat it another million times
because it does not get more complicated
than that just follow the trend the
second thing is that I need to be buying
at a strong area of Interest which
either a strong support strong
resistance level and then the third
point you need to have your entry signal
without your entry signal how do you
know it's the right time to enter the
trade now I will not take a trade unless
I have all three of those foundations
within the trade this is what I call a
standard in my trades because every
single trade that I take is a good trade
no trade that I will risk money on is a
bad trade that simply makes no sense
every single trade that I take is a
lowrisk trade meaning that the odds of
that trade losing are slim to none so in
the trading Niche lowrisk means High
reward not highrisk high reward that's
not how this works if your trade is a
lowrisk trade that means that it has a
high probability of it going in your
favor so for these type of Trades is
where I can risk any anywhere from 20 to
$30,000 $40,000 depends on where the
account is at that point in time now
that you understand that that is why I
simply only take either one to two
trades a week Max maybe and whenever I
trade it doesn't take any more than
about an hour out of my Daye and
obviously this wasn't like this all the
time obviously at the beginning I put in
a lot of time into the markets to
understand the flow of it and how it
works but now over the years I know
exactly when the market is going to move
and when it's not going to move so I
simply only focus on the time when it's
going to move when there's a good trade
possibility so when you learn these key
foundations trading becomes so easy so
now that you understand that let me
actually show you what I mean by getting
into the charts right so right here we
have the trade that I took on January
25th you can see all the way down here
how you can see Thursday the 25th of
January 2024 at about 8:00 in the
morning is when I ended up taking this
trade and if you notice I entered
multiple positions because I am
following the trend I am continua where
the market is going going I'm not trying
to catch a falling knife as the market
is going down I'm like okay now it has
to stop and it has to reverse that is so
hard why would you want to catch a
falling knife if the knife is going down
you simply just push it down you make it
continue to go faster to the downside
that's exactly what we did here and if
something is rising to the upside we
simply just push it up we go with it we
don't want to go against it so as of
right here you can tell how EUR USD on
the higher time frames such as the daily
time frame such as the weekly time frame
all time frames at this point of when
taking this trade right around here it
was heading to the downside you can see
how we have a big left head and a right
shoulder and how we retested the neet
line retested the EMA retested structure
point if we go down to the 4our you can
see how we're rejecting the 4our EMA
we're having a 4-Hour bearish engulfing
Candlestick everything that we would
look into getting into a trade it's
happening at this very point right in
front of us as you can see we have the
rejection from the EMA the rejection
from the structure when we go down to
the lower time time frames this is where
we would actually be looking to enter
the trade because again I use the higher
time frames to understand of where the
market is headed is headed up or is it
heading down after we understand that it
is heading down and that is where we
would go into the lower time frames to
actually look for a very precise and a
very tight entry because if you were to
take a trade based off of the higher
time frames you would need a bigger take
profit a bigger stop loss and that
doesn't really work at the level that
I'm trading right now because it would
require a lot more money I'm talking
like hundreds of millions of dollars now
that I'm trading eight figures you can
use on the lower time frames and it
works perfectly fine so this is where I
entered the trade right here on the 30
minute time frame pretty much once it
created a left head and a right shoulder
and right around this area as soon as I
started seeing the rejections right
before New York session this is where I
entered the trade I have a beautiful
entry confirmation right here on my
bearish engulfing and then I simply
continued to follow the trend and this
is as simple as it gets follow the trend
find a pattern on the higher time frames
find an area of Interest which could be
rejection of a support of resistance or
rejection the previous structure level
or use an extra indicator as an added
confidence now if the EMA is above or
under what I still have not taken this
trade and the answer yes the EMA is a
simple add-on to the actual trade that
I'm taking doesn't matter if it would
have been above or under it doesn't
Define if I take the trade or not my
main core principles in the trade are
going to be the trend the area of
interest and my entry signal and as you
can see this trade had all three of them
now when you add a head and shoulders
pattern when you add the EMA when you
add the shifter structure all of this
stuff this is what is called a lowrisk
trade because you have a series of
confluences going into this trade so it
can go in your direction versus the
other so before I take the actual trade
I have to ask myself what what am I
willing to risk on this trade if it goes
in my favor or not and I usually risk
anywhere from 10 20 to maybe $30,000 in
this trade I actually happen to risk
risk $30,000 on this trade which was a
about normal risk because I always use a
minimum of a 1 to2 risk reward so if I
were to risk $30,000 the minimum that I
have to gain when I win is $60,000 this
trade just happens to go to a one to3
risk to reward where it gave me the
$90,000 in profit because I usually stop
it at a 1 to2 but in this trade I
applied the set and forget and it played
out extremely well and the trend
continued to go to the downside if I
would have continue to H this trade I
could have easily made over
$250,000 but I was not looking for that
in this trade I stuck to my plan and I
cut my profits at where I was ready to
close them and if the trade continued to
go down I was perfectly fine with it
because I was content with the profits
that I was going to make and if I'm
basing My overall direction in the
market let's say with the daily time
frame and that is the area of interest
that I'm rejecting from in order to
enter the trade then I have to set daily
take profits so if I'm selling at a
daily resistance level I have to get out
of the trade at a daily support level
that exactly what we did the next
structure level was a strong level of
support where price could have had a
rejection from to then go back and head
to the upside that is exactly what it
did surprise hit my takeprofit to the T
came back into my entry and then
continued to head to the downside this
is extremely key because if you're going
to be selling at a daily area of
interest do not place a 1-h hour
takeprofit you continue going where the
overall direction of the market is going
to be if I have a weekly area of
Interest then I would place a weekly
take profit now keep in mind the higher
the area of Interest the higher the time
that you have to wait for it to get
there I like to have a weekly or daily
area of interest because the trade can
play out in either 1 to 4 days this one
is having to move really really fast in
Just 4 hours and this trade despite
showing it all over Instagram and
everybody in my telegram everybody in my
DMs that they actually caught the trade
live with me because I actually showed
the trade when I take it before I show
as soon as I take it I show the during
and then obviously the after all of the
students that were in the Sunday swings
call that I host a call every single
week I showed this pair in my top three
analysis that I was going to trade for
the week and this is why my students
make anywhere from $1,000 to $11,500 a
week using the set and forget strategy
and this is because I literally get on a
call with you guys every single week
where I show you my top two three pairs
that I trade and you guys can have the
same exact results as me if you're
wondering what set and forget is and if
you want to know more about it simply
click the link below I have a video
there for you that explains exactly what
we are about and how it Els anywhere
from my students to make anywhere from
,000 to $11,500 a week as a beginner set
and forget Trader I hope this video was
useful for you guys if you guys want to
see any more videos make sure you guys
go check the other videos in my channel
which are extremely educational if you
want to know more about the set and
forget simply click the link in the
description below and I'll see you guys
in the next video see you guys